Guide to the University of Chicago Department of Anthropology Records 1929-1997
University of Chicago Library
- Series IX: Finance
  - Subseries 3: National Science Foundation [NSF]
    - NSF- Brain Research Account [Closed], 1953-1955 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - NSF- Human Population Studies in the Fertile Crescent Account, 1954-1955 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - NSF- Skull Research, 1955 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - NSF- Achenlian Man Research [Closed], 1957 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - NSF- Darwinian Conference, 1957 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - NSF- Darwinian Conference, 1959 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - NSF- Vegetation Study, 1955-1960 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Wolf, Eric- NSF Mexico Archeology Conference, 1960 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - NSF, Cooperative Graduate Fellowships, 1960-1961 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Jacobs, Alan H. [NSF], 1960-1962 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - NSF, [National Science Foundation], 1959-1963 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - NSF- Cooperative Graduate Fellowships, 1962-1963 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Binford, Lewis R. [NSF], 1963 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Jelinek, Arthur [NSF], 1962-1963 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Leacock, Seth [NSF], 1962-1963 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Tax, Sol [NSF], 1963 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - NSF Graduate Fellows Accounts, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - NSF, Cooperative Graduate Fellowships, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - NSF, Cooperative Graduate Fellowships, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Kleindienst, [Haldeman] Maxine R. [NSF], 1961-1964 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - NSF Graduate Fellows Accounts, 1964-1965 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Schlegel, Stuart [NSF], 1965 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Warren- NSF Fellows, 1964-1965 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - National Science Foundation [NSF], 1966 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - NSF- Dissertation Fellowship Grants Awarded, 1965-1967 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Harbinger Kamau, Lucy Jayne [NSF], 1964-1967 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Ortiz, Alfronso A. [NSF] 1965-1962 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Pandey, Triloki [NSF], 1966-1967 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Paul, Sherry (Ortner) [NSF], 1966-1967 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Becker, Ellen [NSF Research Grant], 1965-1968 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Cartmill, Matthew, [NSF], 1965-1968 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Hopkins, Nicholas S. [NSF]1963-1968 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Morris, Craig [NSF], 1966-1968 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Wadley, Susan [NSF], 1967-1968 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Anderson, Robert [NSF Grant], 1967-1969 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Daniels, Robert E. [NSF Research], 1963-1969 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Evett, Daniel [NSF] 1968-1969 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Gerald, Rex [NSF], 1965-1969 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Hyman, Gerald [NSF, NIMH], 1967-1969 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Kracke, Waud [NSF], 1966-1969 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Block Grant [NSF], 1968-1969 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Ostor, Akos, [NSF], 1966-1969 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Paul, Robert [NSF], 1966-1969 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Raymond T. [NSF], 1967-1969 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Spencer, Nancy [NSF], 1966-1969 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Winzeler, Robert E. [NSF], 1966-1969 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Winzeler, Robert L. [NSF], 1966-1969 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Wolf, Linda [NSF], 1965-1969 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Barnett, Stephen A. [NSF Grant], 1965-1970 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Barkow, Jerome [NSF], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Clark, Geoffrey A. [NSF], 1968-1970 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Furbee, Nonnie Luanna, [NSF], 1970 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Hopkins, Joseph III, [NSF], 1968-1970 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Nash, Manning [NSF Grant], 1965-1970 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Price, David [NSF], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Price, P. David [NSF], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Salzman, Philip [NSF], 1966-1970 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Buikstra, Jane [NSF], 1969-1970 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Foster, Rand [NSF], 1970-1971 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Kessinger, T.G. [NSF], 1970-1971 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Raymond T. [NSF], 1966-1971 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Wheatcroft, Wilson [NSF], 1965-1971 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Hinnant, John [NSF, NIMH], 1967-1972 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Possehl, Gregory, [NSF], 1970-1972 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Cook, Thomas [NSF] 1971-1973 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Larsen, Curtis [NSF], 1973 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Fallers, Lloyd A. [NSF] 1964-1974 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Fritz, Margaret [NSF], 1965-1974 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Hecht, Julia [NSF], 1972-1974 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Shore, Brad [NSF], 1972-1974 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Sussman, Randall [NSF], 1974 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Batteau, Allen W. [NSF], 1973-1975 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Batteau, Allen W. [NSF], 1973-1975 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Deveer, Henrietta (Talvitie) [NSF], 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Flataker, Catherine [NSF], 1975 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Foldes, Steven [NSF], 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Hawkins, John P. [NSF], 1972-1975 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Klein, Richard G.- Associate Professor [NSF], 1973-1975 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Klein, Richard G.- Associate Professor [NSF], 1973-1975 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Ohel, Milla Y. [NSF, Wenner Gren], 1975 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Stocking, George [NSF, NEH], 1972-1975 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Warren, Merrily [NSF], 1974-1975 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Butzer, Karl [NSF], 1974-1976 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Daniel, Sheryl B. [NSF], 1974-1976 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Erdman, Joan L. [NSF], 1975-1976 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Galaty, John [NSF], 1974-1976 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Harrold, Francis B. [NSF], 1975-1976 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Rumsey, Alan L. [NSF], 1974-1976 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Thornton, Robert [NSF], 1972-1976 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Daniel, Errol Valentine [NSF, Wenner Gren], 1974-1977 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Freeman, Leslie [NSF], 1970-1977 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - McQuown, Norman [NSF], 1973-1977 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Straus, Lawrence G. [NSF], 1973-1977 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Urciuoli, Bonnie Ann [NSF], 1977 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Volman, Thomas [NSF], 1976-1977 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Cohn, Bernard S. [NSF], 1974-1978 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Feinup-Riordan, Ann [NSF, NIMH], 1975-1978 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Kirkpatrick, John [NSF] 1975-1978 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Maxwell, Joseph [NSF], 1974-1978 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Moore, Melinda [NSF, NIH Proposal], 1978 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Raymond T. [NSF, USPHS], 1974-1978 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Tuttle, Russel, NSF Pending, 1974-1978 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Cohn, Bernard S. [NSF Grant] (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Nagatoshi, Konrad [NSF] (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Satnick, Richard [NSF], 1977-1979 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Miller, David E. [NSF, Wenner Gren], 1978-1980 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Briggs, Charles [NSF, NIMH, Wenner Gren], 1979-1981 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Downey, Gary [NSF], 1979-1981 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Lipuma, Edward [NSF], 1978-1981 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - McKinnon, Susan [NSF], 1978-1983 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Ayres, Mary [NSF], 1979-1983 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Carucci, Lawrence [NSF] (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Kolata, Alan [NSF], 1988 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Kolata, Alan [NSF and NEH],1989-1990 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Kolata, Alan L. [NSF Grant], 1988-1990 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Howell, F. Clark [NSF], 1961-1992 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 4: National Institute of Mental Health [NIMH, USPHS, NIH]
    - USPHS- Dahlberg, 1954-1955 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - USPHS- Dental Research- Dahlberg, 1955-1956 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Tax, Sol- USPHS Medical Research, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Hotchkiss, John C. [NIMH], 1960-1961 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - USPHS- Dental Research- Dahlberg, 1960-1961 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Iwanska (-Wagner), Alicja [NIMH], 1961-1962 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Brown, Leonard K. [NIMH], 1961-1963 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Brown, Leonard K. [NIMH], 1962-1963 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Damas, David [NIMH], 1960-1963 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Sarles, Harvey B. [USPHS], 1962-1963 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Training Grant Accounting, 1963-1964 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Gearing, Fred [NIMH], 1960-1964 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - NIMH Fellow Expenses, 1963-1964 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Training Gran Accounting, 1964-1965 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - USPHS [NIH] General Fellowship Expenses, 1964-1965 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Newton, Esther [NIMH], 1965-1966 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - NIH Grant- Predoctoral Fellows- Department. of Anthropology, 1963-1966 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Carroll, Vern [NIMH], 1963-1966 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Training Grant #3011 Accounting, 1965-1966 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Sider, Karen Blu [USPHS], 1966 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Cronin, Constance [NIMH], 1966-1967 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Kaplan, Irving [NIMH], 1964-1967 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Leaf, Murray [NIMH], 1963-1967 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Pease, Phyllis A. [NIMH], 1965-1967 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Shack, William A. [NIMH] 1963-1967 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Shepardson, Mary [NIMH] 1964-1967 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Spiro, Melford E. [NIMH], 1965-1967 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Training Grant Accounting, 1966-1967 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Alexander, Jack (NIMH), 1968 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Devore, Paul Leonard [NIMH], 1968 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Douglas, William A. [NIMH], 1965-1968 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Friedrich, Margaret [NIMH], 1966-1968 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Owens, Raymond [USPHS], 1968 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Rosen, Lawrence [NIMH], 1966-1968 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Training Grant Allocations, 1967-1968 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Training Grant Accounting, 1967-1968 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Bernstein, Howard B. [NIMH], 1969 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Chock, Phyllis [NIMH], 1969 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Dahlberg, Albert A. [NIH], 1964-1969 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Fabian, Ilona [NIMH], 1968-1969 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Jordan, David [NIMH], 1966-1968 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Jordan, David [NIMH], 1964-1969 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - MacHattie, Susan [NIMH], 1969 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Meeker, Michael [NIMH], 1966-1969 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Meeker, Michael [NIMH], 1966-1969 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Tubesing, Richard L. [NIMH], 1968-1969 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Training Grant Accounting, 1968-1969 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Banks, David (NIMH), 1966-1970 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Blank, Judith (NIMH), 1966-1970 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - David, Kenneth A. (NIMH), 1967-1970 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Foner, Nancy (NIMH), 1968-1970 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Geertz, Clifford (NIMH), 1963-1970 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Hagens, Elizabeth (USPHS), 1970 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Mayhall, John T. (NIMH), 1968-1970 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - McGilvray, Dennis B. (NIMH), 1968-1970 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Rubinyi, Lois, (NIMH), 1968-1970 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Shapiro, Jill (Dubisch) (NIMH), 1965-1970 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Stern, Judith (NIMH), 1967-1970 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Straight, H. Stephen, (NIMH), 1968-1970 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Szanton, David (NIMH), 1966-1970 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Wheeler, Mary Jo, (NIMH), 1968-1970 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Training Grant Accounting, 1969-1970 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Dichter, Thomas C. 1969-1971 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Drummond, Julius A. (Lee), (NIMH), 1968-1971 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Dubetsky, Allen R. (NIMH), 1969-1971 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Dubisch (Shapiro) Jill, (NIMH), 1967-1971 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Eikelman, Dale (NIMH), 1968-1971 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Kershaw, Gretha S. (NIMH), 1970-1971 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Labby, David (NIMH), 1970-1971 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Montague, Susan (NIMH), 1971 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Rabinow, Paul (NIMH), 1966-1971 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Reminick, Ronald (NIMH), 1967-1971 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Rodman, William (NIMH), 1969-1971 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Rodman, William (NIMH), 1969-1971 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Schneider, David M. (NIMH), 1961-1971 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Schiefflin, Edward (NIMH), 1965-1971 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Progress Report Materials (NIH), 1970-1971 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Training Grant Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Training Gran Recommendations, 1970-1971 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Conkling, Robert H. (NIMH), 1972 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Fabrega, Horatio (USPHS), 1972 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Rosen, Charles Bernard (NIMH), 1970-1972 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Whitehead, Harriett (NIMH), 1969-1972 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Training Grant Progress Report, 1963-1972 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Training Grant Budget and Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Attinasi, John (NIMH), 1970-1973 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Benedict, Peter (NIMH), 1967-1973 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Bernstein, Howard (NIMH), 1970-1973 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Boon, James (NIMH), 1971-1973 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Brown, Jennifer (NIMH), 1971-1973 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Feinberg, Richard (NIMH), 1971-1973 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Fischer, Michael (NIMH), 1968-1973 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, Clarke, (USPHS), 1972-1973 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Mullings, Leith (NIMH), 1966-1973 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Schneider, David M. (NIMH), 1970-1973 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Blackmon, Marilyn Hughs (NIMH), 1972-1974 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Good, Byron Joseph, (USPHS), 1972-1974 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - NIMH Training Grant Policy, 1966-1974 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Eaton, Marian (NIMH), 1975 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Training Grant, 1971-1975 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Training Grant Progress Report, 1972-1975 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Hall, Henry J. (NIMH), 1974-1976 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Pessar, Patricia (NIMH), 1971-1976 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Prosnitz, David T. (NIMH), 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Urban, Gregory (NIMH), 1972-1976 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Gorman, Michael (NIMH), 1977 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Kemper, Steven E.G. (NIMH), 1969-1977 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - MacKenzie, Margaret A. (NIH), 1970-1977 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Early, Evelyn (NIMH), 1974-1978 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Training Grant Proposal, 1973-1978 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Davis, Christopher (NIMH), 1973-1978 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Soiffer, Stephen (NIMH), 1974-1979 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Blanchard, David (NIMH), 1976-1982 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Leavitt, John (NIMH), 1980-1984 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Roberts, Allen F. (NIMH), 1974-1988 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 5: Other Faculty and Student Grants
    - Department. Funds for Research Accounting, 1929-1936 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - National Academy of Science Account, 1949 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Foundation- Ethnology, Linguistics and Archeology Fund, 1949 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Foundation- Redfield Trip to China, 1949 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Viking Fund- Tax, 1949 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Washburn, S.L.- Weidenreich Memorial Volume (Viking Fund), 1949 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Viking Fund #5, 1949 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Viking Fund, 1944-1949 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Viking Fund, 1950 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Viking Fund, 1949-1950 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Tama Iowa Farm Account, 1949-1950 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Fort Berthold Study, 1950-1952 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Viking Fund, 1951-1952 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Wenner Gren Publication Fund, 1953 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Wenner Gren African Research, 1952-1953 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Wenner Gren- Raymond Firth, 1955 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Viking Fund #8, 1949-1957 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Fox Indian Professional Educational Program, 1958 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Viking Fund, 1958 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Wenner Gren Visiting Professor Fund, 1958 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Gerald E.- Rockefeller Sumatra Research, 1959 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Tax, Sol- Wenner-Gren Darwin Centennial, 1960 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - NDEA Title IV, Foreign language Fellowship, 1958-1960 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller Foundation- Visiting Professors, 1959-1961 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Wenner Gren Visiting Professor Fund, 1958-1961 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - NDEA Title IV Fellowships, 1960-1961 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - NDEA Title IV, 1960-1961 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - NDEA Anthropology, 1960-1961 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - NDEA Title IV, Budget, 1960-1961 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Rockafeller Foundation Visiting Professors, 1962 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Tax, Sol- Summer Workshop on American Indian Affairs, 1962 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Tax, Sol- Carnegie Corp. Cross-Cultural Education Project, 1962 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Tax, Sol- American Indian Charter Convention, 1961-1962 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Wenner-Gren- Das, 1961-1962 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - NDEA Title IV, 1960-1962 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - NDEA Title IV, Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - NDEA Title IV, 1961-1962 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - NDEA Anthropology, 1961-1962 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - NDEA Title IV, Budget, 1961-1962 (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - Rockefeller Visiting Professors, 1963 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - NDEA Title IV, 1962-1963 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - NDEA Anthropology, 1962-1963 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - NDEA Title IV, Budget, 1962-1963 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - NDEA Title IV, Investigator's Report, 1962-1963 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - NDEA Title IV, Program Report, 1962-1963 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Rockafeller Foundation Visiting Professor Program, 1963-1964 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Rockafeller Visiting Professor Program, 1957-1964 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Schneider- Ford Foundation Behavioral Sciences in Anthropology, 1964 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Sytek, William [Noyes Scholarship], 1960-1964 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - NDEA Title IV, Application Forms, 1961-1964 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - NDEA Title IV, 1963-1964 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - NDEA Anthropology, 1963-1964 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - NDEA Title IV, Investigator's Report, 1963-1964 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Fellows, 1964-1965 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Visiting Professors, 1964-1965 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Cochojil, Remigio Isabel, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - NDEA Title IV, 1964-1965 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - NDEA Anthropology, 1964-1965 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Aaronson, Daniel. 1966 (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - National Academy of Science- National Research Council, 1960-1966 (Box 109, Folder 21)
    - Owuso, Maxwell [Wenner Gren], 1966 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Fisher, James F. (IDF), 1964-1967 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - NDEA Title IV, 1966-1967 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - NDEA Title IV, survey, 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Summer Travel Grants, 1968-1969 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - NDEA Title IV, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - NDEA Title IV, 1968-1969 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Cramer, Douglass [Ford Foundation], 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Robotham, Donald- African Committee Research, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Witherspoon, Gary, 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Varenne, Herve [Wenner Gren], 1970 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Friedrich, Paul [NDEA Title IV], 1967-1970 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Willis, John [NDEA Fulbright Hays], 1964-1970 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - NDEA Title IV, 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Demallie, Raymond [NEH], 1970-1971 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - NDEA Title IV, 1970-1971 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Friedlander, Judith (NDEA Title IV, NIH), 1968-1971 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities- American Indian Studies, 1970-1972 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Masry, Abdullah [Travel Grant], 1972-1973 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Moburg, David, 1972-1973 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - Shoemaker, Robin, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Johanson, Donald Carl [Wenner Gren], 1970-1973 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - Merbs, Charles F. [National Geographic Society], 1966-1974 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - Buchdahl, David. 1971-1975 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Thorp, John. 1975 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Wood, Ananda E. [Wenner Gren], 1972-1975 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Prindle, Carol. [SSRC] 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Druke, Mary A. [Other], 1976 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Barnhart, Elizabeth, 1977 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Cohn, Bernard S. 1974-1978 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Cohn, Bernard S. (NEH Proposal), 1978 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Stuebe, Fred K. [Wenner Gren], 1978 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Buckley, Thomas C.T. [Wenner Gren] (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Farquhar, Judith. 1982 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Finnegan, Gregory A. 1981-1982 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Anthro at Chicago History of Anthropology Newsletter, George Stocking, 1978-1985 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Cohn, Bernard S. [NEH Pending], 1979-1985 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Stocking, George- History of Anthropology Funds, 1984-1987 (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Kolata- Occidental Oil and Gas Corp. 1989 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Kolata, Alan [NEH], 1988-1990 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Kolata, Alan [NEH Matching Funds], 1989-1990 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Kolata, Alan [NEH], 1991 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Kolata, Alan [NEH/NSF], 1989-1991 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Kolata, Alan NEH Matching and Funds, 1989-1991 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Roy D. Albert Fund and Prize, 1958-1996 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Mayall, John T. undated (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Tax, Sol- Schwarzhaupt Tama Indian Program, undated (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Tax, Sol- Fox Indian Professional Education, undated (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 6: Miscellaneous Finance
    - Equipment, 1952-1953 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Expenses, 1949-1954 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Divisional Expense Account, 1949-1957 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Peyote Religion, The- Book Sales and Receipts, 1956-1958 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Comptroller, 1961 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Roy D. Albert Loan Fund, 1958-1961 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Roy D. Albert Emergency Student Loan Fund, 1958-1962 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Travel, Miscellaneous, 1959-1963 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Quadrangle Club Luncheons, 1962-1963 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Quadrangle Club Luncheons, 1963-1964 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Anthropology, Expense Account, 1963-1964 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Quadrangle Club Luncheons, 1964-1965 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Anthropology Expense Account, (E and E), 1964-1965 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Anthropology Expense Account, (E and E), 1964-1965 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Comptroller, 1963-1966 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Quadrangle Club Luncheons, 1965-1966 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Quadrangle Club, 1966-1967 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Anthropology Library Allocation and Purchases, 1961-1970 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Walker, Philip, 1972 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Dickie, Walter, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Money Possibilities, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Haskell Hall, Remodel Budget, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Archeology Field School, 1981-1982 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Thomas Fallers Memorial Lecture Fund, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Monday Seminar Lecture Series, 1991-1992 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Anthro Incentive Funds, 1990-1992 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Audio-Visual, 1988-1992 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Shoenbrod Memorial Library Fund, 1983, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Anthro Carry Over, 1989-1992 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Quadrangle Club, Faculty Luncheons, 1992-1993 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - U of C Bookstore, 1992-1994 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Endowment Income, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Request for Late Transfer, 1992-1994 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Anthropology E and E, Operating Costs, 1994-1995 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Anthro Recruitment Costs, 1994-1995 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Schoenbrod Memorial Fund, 1978-1995 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Seminars, 1994-1995 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Events- Alumni and Gender Conferences, 1992-1995 (Box 115, Folder 14)